<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Keep On Rolling</title><link>https://keep-on-rolling.ch/en/</link><description>Recent content on Keep On Rolling</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>{{ YEAR }} This work by [Marcus Fihlon](https://fihlon.swiss/) is licensed under [CC BY-SA 4.0](https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-sa/4.0/)</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 12 Mar 2022 10:29:24 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://keep-on-rolling.ch/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Black Friday</title><link>https://keep-on-rolling.ch/en/2022/03/12/black-friday/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Mar 2022 10:29:24 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://keep-on-rolling.ch/en/2022/03/12/black-friday/</guid><description>Freezing cold at -2 °C but sunny - that&amp;rsquo;s how my Friday started. I was really in a good mood, because at least it was dry and the forecast promised for the noon even double-digit plus degrees. After a hearty breakfast I felt sufficiently strengthened and ready for the biggest climb of my four and a half day tour from Lucerne to Brühl near Cologne over a total of 700 km.</description></item><item><title>Redesign &amp; Reboot</title><link>https://keep-on-rolling.ch/en/2022/03/09/redesign-reboot/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 13:52:29 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://keep-on-rolling.ch/en/2022/03/09/redesign-reboot/</guid><description>If you look closely, you may notice some changes on my website. The layout is now more dynamic and adapts better to smartphones and tablets. Besides the language, you can now also choose between a light and a dark appearance. But not only the design has changed, the biggest adjustment took place under the hood:
Instead of Jekyll, I now use Hugo to generate this website from my posts. The configuration is easier and the directory structure is clearer for me.</description></item><item><title>Live</title><link>https://keep-on-rolling.ch/en/live/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2022 16:55:16 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://keep-on-rolling.ch/en/live/</guid><description>When I ride longer tours, I often use the mobile app of LocaToWeb and display my current position on this page. You can then follow me live here, send me messages and look at my photos right after I took them.
Actual live broadcast event There is currently no live broadcast. But I am already planning my next trip. Until this one will begin, you are welcome to watch the past live broadcasts.</description></item><item><title>Videos</title><link>https://keep-on-rolling.ch/en/videos/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2022 16:34:06 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://keep-on-rolling.ch/en/videos/</guid><description>I am experimenting with recording and editing videos about my travels. Actually they are in German, but I will see how I can add English subtitles. For publishing my videos I use my own channel on YouTube:
My YouTube channel
Feedback is highly appreciated!
Yours
Marcus</description></item><item><title>Imprint</title><link>https://keep-on-rolling.ch/en/imprint/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2022 10:30:53 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://keep-on-rolling.ch/en/imprint/</guid><description>Contact Marcus Fihlon
Winkelriedstrasse 25
6003 Luzern
Switzerland
E-Mail: marcus@fihlon.swiss
Privacy All data is loaded from the same server (keep-on-rolling.ch). No data from other servers will be included (also no Facebook, Google, Instagram, Twitter, etc). No data will be stored on your computer (also no cookies).
License This work by Marcus Fihlon is licensed under CC BY-SA 4.0.</description></item><item><title>Keep On Rolling</title><link>https://keep-on-rolling.ch/en/2021/12/26/keep-on-rolling/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Dec 2021 14:11:04 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://keep-on-rolling.ch/en/2021/12/26/keep-on-rolling/</guid><description>New name, new slogan: After a little more than two years, I have now decided to breathe new life into my bikepacking blog with a new name and new slogan. After returning from my tour across the USA with my bicycle in November 2019, first came winter, then Corona. The pandemic has now been in our grip for much longer than we initially thought possible. Of course, this also had an impact on my plans.</description></item></channel></rss>