<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Keep On Rolling</title><link>https://keep-on-rolling.ch/en/</link><description>Recent content on Keep On Rolling</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>{{ YEAR }} This work by [Marcus Fihlon](https://fihlon.swiss/) is licensed under [CC BY-SA 4.0](https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-sa/4.0/)</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://keep-on-rolling.ch/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Gotthard Pass</title><link>https://keep-on-rolling.ch/en/2022/05/22/the-gotthard-pass/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://keep-on-rolling.ch/en/2022/05/22/the-gotthard-pass/</guid><description>On my trip by bike to Venice I come across my fear opponent today: The 2'106 m high Gotthard pass! Actually, the Gotthard pass should have been opened only next Thursday to Ascension Day. But because there was record-breakingly little snow this winter, it was already opened the day before yesterday on Friday, almost a week before. So I was lucky &amp;ndash; or not, because then I would have had a good excuse to take the train through the Gotthard tunnel.</description></item><item><title>To Venice by Bicycle</title><link>https://keep-on-rolling.ch/en/2022/05/21/to-venice-by-bicycle/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://keep-on-rolling.ch/en/2022/05/21/to-venice-by-bicycle/</guid><description>It has already become a tradition: Every year for the past ten years, we&amp;rsquo;ve taken a weekend city trip together. Even during the Corona pandemic, we had always found a solution. This year it was Venice&amp;rsquo;s turn. Thanks to a holiday it even became a long weekend. We, that is besides me Gabi, Gloria, Manu and Dani. With Dani I have already made some day trips by bike and for next year we are planning something huge together.</description></item><item><title>Around Lake Lucerne</title><link>https://keep-on-rolling.ch/en/2022/05/15/around-lake-lucerne/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://keep-on-rolling.ch/en/2022/05/15/around-lake-lucerne/</guid><description>We are lucky, because today is Sunday and as it should be for a Sunday, the sun is shining! &amp;ldquo;We&amp;rdquo; means that I am not alone on the road today, but accompanied by three friends: Tina, Gunnar, and Daniel. At the beginning of the bike season, we meet almost traditionally for a rather leisurely, but quite challenging round around Lake Lucerne. Unfortunately not around the whole lake, because from Bauen up to Seelisberg there is no road, but only a steep hiking trail with 850 stone steps!</description></item><item><title>First Hundred</title><link>https://keep-on-rolling.ch/en/2022/04/17/first-hundred/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://keep-on-rolling.ch/en/2022/04/17/first-hundred/</guid><description>Exactly a week ago at the SlowUp in Ticino I completed the first tour with the new electronic shifting on my gravel bike. That was a very chill little round. Today it&amp;rsquo;s time for a &amp;ldquo;real&amp;rdquo; test, a big ride with a lot of gravel, a lot of forest, a lot of uphill and a long downhill.
I start as so often directly from home in the center of Lucerne. But the ride out of the city is relatively relaxed, I&amp;rsquo;m on a quiet neighborhood road in a few minutes at the Reuss.</description></item><item><title>On the Road Again</title><link>https://keep-on-rolling.ch/en/2022/04/09/on-the-road-again/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://keep-on-rolling.ch/en/2022/04/09/on-the-road-again/</guid><description>Finally, the time has come: My beloved Gravelbike got his new shifting. It sounds so simple. Yet the list of replaced parts is really long (and correspondingly expensive):
New rear derailleur New cassette New chainring New chain New brake and shift levers New front and rear brakes New brake pipes New handlebar tape After the first (not last!) Oiling (the chain) with DryFluid I could not wait to make a first ride and familiarize myself with shifting and braking.</description></item><item><title>Hello SRAM</title><link>https://keep-on-rolling.ch/en/2022/03/17/hello-sram/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://keep-on-rolling.ch/en/2022/03/17/hello-sram/</guid><description>The dice have been thrown. I have made my decision. The parts are ordered. The appointment with the bike mechanic of my confidence is made. After another problem with my rear derailleur and the subsequent decision to replace the rotor rear derailleur is now final that my beloved gravel bike gets an electronic shifting from SRAM.
The conversion will be somewhat larger, since also the chain, the chainring, as well as the brake levers and thus also the brakes must be replaced.</description></item><item><title>Goodbye Rotor</title><link>https://keep-on-rolling.ch/en/2022/03/14/goodbye-rotor/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://keep-on-rolling.ch/en/2022/03/14/goodbye-rotor/</guid><description>Last week the rear derailleur broke during my bikepacking tour from Lucerne to Brühl to attend the JavaLand conference, I had already written about it. I built my gravel bike almost two years ago to the day and this is already the second broken rear derailleur in two years. So slowly I lose confidence in my shifting. But what were my reasons for selecting a Rotor drivetrain, what problems I had and above all, what happens next?</description></item><item><title>Black Friday</title><link>https://keep-on-rolling.ch/en/2022/03/12/black-friday/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://keep-on-rolling.ch/en/2022/03/12/black-friday/</guid><description>Freezing cold at -2 °C but sunny - that&amp;rsquo;s how my Friday started. I was really in a good mood, because at least it was dry and the forecast promised for the noon even double-digit plus degrees. After a hearty breakfast I felt sufficiently strengthened and ready for the biggest climb of my four and a half day tour from Lucerne to Brühl near Cologne over a total of 700 km.</description></item><item><title>Redesign &amp; Reboot</title><link>https://keep-on-rolling.ch/en/2022/03/09/redesign-reboot/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://keep-on-rolling.ch/en/2022/03/09/redesign-reboot/</guid><description>If you look closely, you may notice some changes on my website. The layout is now more dynamic and adapts better to smartphones and tablets. Besides the language, you can now also choose between a light and a dark appearance. But not only the design has changed, the biggest adjustment took place under the hood:
Instead of Jekyll, I now use Hugo to generate this website from my posts. The configuration is easier and the directory structure is clearer for me.</description></item><item><title>Keep On Rolling</title><link>https://keep-on-rolling.ch/en/2021/12/26/keep-on-rolling/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://keep-on-rolling.ch/en/2021/12/26/keep-on-rolling/</guid><description>New name, new slogan: After a little more than two years, I have now decided to breathe new life into my bikepacking blog with a new name and new slogan. After returning from my tour across the USA with my bicycle in November 2019, first came winter, then Corona. The pandemic has now been in our grip for much longer than we initially thought possible. Of course, this also had an impact on my plans.</description></item><item><title>Imprint</title><link>https://keep-on-rolling.ch/en/imprint/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://keep-on-rolling.ch/en/imprint/</guid><description>Contact Marcus Fihlon
Winkelriedstrasse 25
6003 Luzern
Switzerland
E-Mail: marcus@fihlon.swiss
Privacy All data is loaded from the same server (keep-on-rolling.ch). No data from other servers will be included (also no Facebook, Google, Instagram, Twitter, etc). No data will be stored on your computer (also no cookies).
License This work by Marcus Fihlon is licensed under CC BY-SA 4.0. The content is prepared by the Hugo Framework (Apache License 2.0) and the Anatole Theme (MIT License) is used.</description></item><item><title>Live</title><link>https://keep-on-rolling.ch/en/live/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://keep-on-rolling.ch/en/live/</guid><description>When I ride longer tours, I often use the mobile app of LocaToWeb and display my current position on this page. You can then follow me live here, send me messages and look at my photos right after I took them.
Actual live broadcast event There is currently no live broadcast. But I am already planning my next trip. Until this one will begin, you are welcome to watch the past live broadcasts.</description></item><item><title>Videos</title><link>https://keep-on-rolling.ch/en/videos/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://keep-on-rolling.ch/en/videos/</guid><description>I am experimenting with recording and editing videos about my travels. Actually they are in German, but I will see how I can add English subtitles. For publishing my videos I use my own channel on YouTube:
My YouTube channel
Feedback is highly appreciated!
Yours
Marcus</description></item></channel></rss>