<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>venice-2022 on Keep On Rolling</title><link>https://keep-on-rolling.ch/en/series/venice-2022/</link><description>Recent content in venice-2022 on Keep On Rolling</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>{{ YEAR }} This work by [Marcus Fihlon](https://fihlon.swiss/) is licensed under [CC BY-SA 4.0](https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-sa/4.0/)</copyright><lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://keep-on-rolling.ch/en/series/venice-2022/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Passo Monte Ceneri</title><link>https://keep-on-rolling.ch/en/2022/05/23/passo-monte-ceneri/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://keep-on-rolling.ch/en/2022/05/23/passo-monte-ceneri/</guid><description>After I had conquered yesterday the Gotthard pass, today immediately the second highest pass of my trip by bike to Venice comes up to me: The Passo Monte Ceneri! The railroad and also the motorists on the highway have it again very easy and go down through a tunnel to the other side. I have of course chosen the way over the top!
After the effort yesterday, the night was definitely too short.</description></item><item><title>The Gotthard Pass</title><link>https://keep-on-rolling.ch/en/2022/05/22/the-gotthard-pass/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://keep-on-rolling.ch/en/2022/05/22/the-gotthard-pass/</guid><description>On my trip by bike to Venice I come across my fear opponent today: The 2'106 m high Gotthard pass! Actually, the Gotthard pass should have been opened only next Thursday to Ascension Day. But because there was record-breakingly little snow this winter, it was already opened the day before yesterday on Friday, almost a week before. So I was lucky &amp;ndash; or not, because then I would have had a good excuse to take the train through the Gotthard tunnel.</description></item><item><title>To Venice by Bicycle</title><link>https://keep-on-rolling.ch/en/2022/05/21/to-venice-by-bicycle/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://keep-on-rolling.ch/en/2022/05/21/to-venice-by-bicycle/</guid><description>It has already become a tradition: Every year for the past ten years, we&amp;rsquo;ve taken a weekend city trip together. Even during the Corona pandemic, we had always found a solution. This year it was Venice&amp;rsquo;s turn. Thanks to a holiday it even became a long weekend. We, that is besides me Gabi, Gloria, Manu and Dani. With Dani I have already made some day trips by bike and for next year we are planning something huge together.</description></item></channel></rss>